Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- [Name is scratched out] Photo taken by O.A. Roorbach, publisher of Dramatic Photographers, 122 Nassau Street, New York, New York (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 249)
- "The Iconoclast" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 250)
- "Marie Antoinette" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 251)
- "Lady Blessing" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 252)
- Caroline Coit (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 253)
- R.M. Parurelee (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 254)
- Girl (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 255)
- Original photo of a young man. Photo taken by J. Ludovici's Studio & Photographic Gallery, A. Gillin, Photographer, 889 Broadway, New York, New York & Bellevue Avenue, Newport, RI (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 256)
- "Little All Right" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 257)
- Photo of a man in an album marked "1875" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 258)
- Original tintype of a family (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 259)
- Original photo of a man taken by Greene, Cleveland, OH (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 260)
- Original photo of a woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 261)
- Original photo of a man (same man 00260) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 262)
- Allan Sankey, 1878 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 263)
- Photo of a girl taken by Dabbs, 174 Liberty Street, Pittsburgh, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 264)
- Original photo of a boy and girl taken by Dabbs, 174 Liberty Street, Pittsburgh, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 265)
- Evelyn Louise Foster, 1873 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 266)
- Evelyn Louise Foster, 1882 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 267)
- Original tintype of 3 children with initials ELF, ER, and LR, October 17, 1878 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 268)
- Evelyn Louise Foster, 1875 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 269)
- "Medora" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 270)
- Original tintype of a little girl, 1879 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 271)
- Original photo of a girl taken by Dabbs, 174 Liberty Street, Pittsburgh, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 272)
- Jessie Schulten (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 273)
- Sketch including a family and butler on the steps of a building. Photo labeled "Charity" on rear in pencil (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 274)
- Original photo of a girl taken by Sonnenberg, 133 Ohio Street, Allegheny City, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 275)
- Original photo of a woman taken by Dabbs, 174 Liberty Street, Pittsburgh, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 276)
- Drawing depicting and labeled "The Dead Christ" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 277)
- Drawing of a smile cat with labeled "Ha-Ha-Ha, I've Eaten The Canary" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 278)
- Original photo of the Thumb family including Mr., Mrs. and baby (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 279)
- Original drawing of "Napoleon" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 280)
- Drawing depicting a family, published by The New York Photographic Company, No. 453, Broadway, New York, New York (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 281)
- Drawing of a cat and fish bowl. The cat is trying to catch the fish in the bowl. Labeled "The Fishing Party" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 282)
- Drawing depicting "The Princess of France" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 283)
- Original photo of a girl sitting on a table top (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 284)
- Original tintype of a man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 285)
- Drawing of a horse inside a horseshoe (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 286)
- Harry Lightner's children [2 girls and a boy] taken by Bradley & Rulofson, Montgomery Street, San Francisco, CA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 287)
- Evelyn Louise Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 288)
- Mrs. Lucy Rutherford Hays, 1878 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 289)
- Mr. Rutherford B. Hays, "President of the United States 1877-1881" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 290)
- C.W. Couldock (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 291)
- C.W. Couldock, 1890 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 292)
- Mrs. C. William Lightner (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 293)
- C. William Lightner (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 294)
- Thomas Bayard (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 295)
- General W.S. Hancock, June 29, 1880 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 296)
- Charley Keyes, age 2 years 3 months, 1879 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 297)
- 1" X 2" tintype of a woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 298)
- Minstrel W. Rattray, taken by Artist & Photographer, 58, Bold Street, Liverpool. Signed "J.P. Crocker" in pencil on rear (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 299)
- Minstrel J.P. Crocker, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 300)
- Photo of Prince of Wales Minstrels, Proprietors - Rawlinson & Ernest, Cox photo. The Peerless Tenors.Includes [Jon] Brown, C. Ernest, J.P. Collins, and John Rawlinson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 301)
- Photo of minstrel Charlie Pette[rf]ill taken by Bogardus Photographer, 363 Broadway, Cor. Franklin St., New York (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 302)
- Minstrel Sam Ne[vl]in? (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 303)
- Alfred Wigam, "English actor and manager. Not a minstrel" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 304)
- Minstrel Wash Norton, 1861 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 305)
- Minstrel John Rawlinson, minstrel, ballad singer and general performer, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 306)
- Minstrel, photo taken by London Stereoscopic Company (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 307)
- Minstrel, photo taken by A. William, Photo Hornsey (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 308)
- Minstrel Jean Ritter and other Christy minstrels (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 309)
- Minstrel Jean Ritter, prima donna with Moore, Crocker, Ritter & Hamilton, Christy Minstrels, England, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 310)
- Minstrel Jean Ritter. "Moore, Crocker, Ritter & Hamilton, England, minstrels", 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 311)
- Unnamed minstrel (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 312)
- Minstrel Dan Bryant, 1860 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 313)
  Pittcat ML420 B838 P56 1860.
- Minstrel Pony Moore (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 314)
- John L. Toole, famous comedian, not a minstrel (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 315)
- Johnny Pell of Morris Bros. Pell and Trowbridge Minstrels, Boston, MA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 316)
- E.J. Melville, Jig dancer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 317)
- Minstrel Hickery. English Eccentric but not famous (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 318)
- Minstrel Hickery. English Eccentric but not famous (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 319)
- Minstrel Billy Morris of Pell and Trowbridge, Boston, MA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 320)
- Minstrel Billy Morris of Pell and Trowbridge, Boston, MA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 321)
- Minstrel Billy Morris of Pell and Trowbridge, Boston, MA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 322)
- Minstrel Billy Morris of Pell and Trowbridge, Boston, MA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 323)
- Fiddle player (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 324)
- 'The Great Leon' Female Impersonator and prima donna. Kelly & Leon's Minstrels (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 325)
- Minstrel Dan Bryant (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 326)
- Frank B. Converse, famous banjoist and Tommy Peel, noted jig dancer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 327)
- Johnny Queen, jig and clog dancer and general performer. "Excellent example of the jig (and also the clog costume)" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 328)
- Minstrel, possibly Rainford (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 329)
- Minstrel Dave Reed. "Traveled with Spaulding & Rogers River Circus Mississippi and Ohio Rivers. 50s_ in the nineties appeared with vaudeville with wife and grown up children as the Reed Birds" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 330)
- Sam Norris (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 331)
- Minstrel Chas. Wallace, Australian minstrel and fine singer of ballads (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 332)
- Minstrel Billy Morris of Pell and Trowbridge, Boston, Mass, 50s-60s (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 333)
- Minstrel Rick Cappoll (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 334)
- Minstrel Lou Morris, "Morris Bros, Pell and Trowbridge minstrels, Boston, MA" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 335)
- Minstrel Lou Morris (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 336)
- Minstrel Frank Meade (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 337)
- Minstrel Dick Pelham, "right name Pell-no relation to Johnny Pell. One of the original Virginia minstrels-first in N.Y. and London. This is a poor picture. He remains in England permanently" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 338)
- Minstrels George and William Guy, 1867 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 339)
- "Jenny Moore" as a little girl (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 340)
- Sam Correll (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 341)
- Harry Herbert (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 342)
- Dick Lindton (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 343)
- James Nilling (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 344)
- Photo of a man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 345)
- Photo of a man. Question mark appears on rear of photo on pencil (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 346)
- Photo of a man. Question mark appears on rear of photo on pencil (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 347)
- Minstrel Jean Ritter, associated with Moore, Crocker Ritter and Hamilton, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 348)
- Photo of minstrel Tony [Bish}, "Violinist and musical director Moore, Crocker, Ritter, Hamilton. Christy Minstrels, England", 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 349)
- Minstrel Tony Nish, "Violinist and musical director, Raynor & Pierce, Christy Minstrels", 1859 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 350)
- Tintype of John L. Stroub. Question mark on rear of photo along with "Don't know him" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 351)
- Eph Horn. "Deleneator and Tamborinist at Woods minstrels" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 352)
- Geo. Wilson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 353)
- Lew Collins. Signed "Yours Truly, Lew Collins" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 354)
- Tintype of John Allen (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 355)
- Tony Pastor. Signed "To my friend A.W. Moore, Tony Pastor" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 356)
- Tony Pastor. Signed "With kind regards, to my friend A.W. Moore, from Tony Pastor" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 357)
- G.W. Moore, "Pony Moore, Moore & Burgess, Minstrel" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 358)
- Billy Pastor, "brother of Tony." Photo taken by Photographic Artists, J. Gurney and Son, 707 Broadway N.Y. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 359)
- Sam Newlin "Minstrel not famous" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 360)
- Mr. Bayae Senior (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 361)
- Lou Morris, "Morris Bros, Pell and Trowbridge Minstrels, Boston, MA" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 362)
- Lou Morris, "Morris Bros, Pell and Trowbridge Minstrels, Boston, MA" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 363)
- Edwin Holmes, "with Dupres and Benedick (W.S.)", 1867 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 364)
- Donaldson & Crocker (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 365)
- J.P. Brocker, "Moore, Crocker, Ritter & Hamilton, Christy Minstrels, England", 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 366)
- J.W. Moore, "Pony Moore, Moore & Burgess Minstrels, London" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 367)
- Lou Morris, "Morris Bros, Pell and Trowbridge Minstrels, Boston Mass" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 368)
- Lou Morris, "Morris Bros, Pell and Trowbridge Minstrels, Boston Mass" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 369)
- Jesse Williams, "with Moore, Crocker, Ritter & Hamilton. England", 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 370)
- Unknown minstrel taken by J. Hatherill, Photographer (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 371)
- Minstrel, "not among the celebrated" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 372)
- Melville, Steel, and Norton, members of the Christy's Minstrels (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 373)
- James (Jim) Unsworth, "Banjoist and comique par excellance" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 374)
- Johnny Pell, "of Morris Bros., Pell and Trowbridge Minstrels, Boston Mass" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 375)
- Jim Hartley? Photo taken by Hennah & Kent, 108 King's Road, Brighton (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 376)
- E. Horn (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 377)
- Berk Bradshaw and Lou Hyndman in conversation, outside. The corner of a building is in the photo along with a lot of greenery (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 378)
- Campbell, Reecie, Bessie, Sarah, Aunt Mary, and Cousin Jo Robb with 2 children posing for the shot (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 379)
- Reecie and Sarah Campbell holding hands and posing for the shot (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 380)
- Mary and Bessie Cooper facing the camera, one leaning on the other (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 381)
- Henrietta Crosman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 382)
  - Henrietta Crossman, 1899 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 382.01)
    Leading lady of Harry Davis' Stock Company, Pittsburgh PA
  - Henrietta Crossman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 382.02)
  - Henrietta Crossman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 382.03)
  - Henrietta Crossman in an unidentified play posed with a man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 382.04)
  - Henrietta Crossman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 382.05)
- Henrietta Crosman, wearing a large hat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 383)
- George Denniston, Franklin Bigelow, and Charles Walton standing together outside in a flower garden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 384)
- Eliza Olva Denniston and Aunt Hannah Harrison posing together on the boardwalk, 1901 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 385)
- Edith Darlington-Denniston (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 386)
- Edith Darlington-Denniston, George Denniston Ghyssels and Evelyn Foster Morneweck (with a fourth individual) in a boat. Atlantic City, NJ (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 387)
- Six unidentified women posing together for the camera on a covered porch (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 388)
- Edith Darlington-Denniston, Don McKay, Cecil Speer and Jeff Hewitt, the two men in dark suits and the two women in light dresses (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 389)
- Six unidentified people (4 girls in light dresses and 2 boys in dark suits) sitting on the lawn and posing for the camera (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 390)
- Evelyn Foster Morneweck sitting at a piano and paging through a large book, in Stuart, Florida, 1964 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 391)
- Photos from F. Laird Snowden, 1963 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 392)
  Letter from Laird and Mary Snowden to Evelyn and Alfred Morneweck dated May 30, 1963, included in folder. Writer describes photos as "taken with my little camera" but does not identify subjects.
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: Four unidentified people (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.01)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: unidentified man and woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.02)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: three unidentified people (2 men, 1 woman) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.03)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: four unidentified people (three men, one woman) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.04)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: four unidentified people in front of a house (3 men 1 woman) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.05)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: four unidentified people in front of a house (three men one woman) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.06)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: unidentified couple (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.07)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: four unidentified people in front of house (three men, one woman) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.08)
  - Photos from F. Laird Snowden: unidentified woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 392.09)
- Mr. and Mrs. Weston G. Morneweck, 1953 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 393)
  Included in folder is a brief blurb from the August 12, 1953, Detroit Free Press describing that it was Mr. and Mrs. Morneweck's 50th anniversary, and a copy of the invitation to their anniversary party.
- Billy B. Foster, December 1958 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 394)
- Don McKay, Don McKay, and Robert Johnson (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 395)
- Denis O'Connor and Kevin Michael at the Stephen Foster Statue, Pittsburgh, June, 1959 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 396)
- Caroline Snowden, May 1861 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 397)
- 8323 Epworth Boulevard (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 398)
  - House located at 8323 Epworth Blvd. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 398.01)
  - House located at 8323 Epworth Blvd (vertical shot) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 398.02)
  - House located at 8323 Epworth Blvd (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 398.03)
  - House located at 8323 Epworth Blvd (shot from across the road) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 398.04)
  - House located at 8323 Epworth Blvd, vertical (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 398.05)
  - House located at 8323 Epworth Blvd (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 398.06)
  - Rebecca S. Foster and Hannah Harrison in front of the house at 8323 Epworth Blvd (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 398.07)
- Four unidentified women on the path to the dock, Brendel Lake, Oakland Co., Michigan (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 399)
- Two women and girl in an automobile in from of the Motor Square Hotel, East Liberty, Pittsburgh (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 400)
- Two women in an automobile in front of the Motor Square Hotel, East Liberty, Pittsburgh (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 401)
- Billy and an unidentified man with their automobile in front of the Motor Square Hotel, Pittsburgh, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 402)
  Two copies
- Portrait of unidentified man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 403)
- Portrait of an unidentified woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 404)
- Portrait of an unidentified boy, seated (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 405)
  Original metal photo
- Miss Ward, Miss Darby at G.C. College (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 406)
  Tiny print (round with less than a 1" circumference).
- Portrait of unidentified boy (Henrietta Crossman's son?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 407)
  Back reads "My little [?] Crosman at six years. Bless him
- Portrait of unidentified boy (Henrietta Crosman's son?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 408)
  Back reads "To my dear great great uncle from Crosman [indecipherable] at six years
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 409)
- Group gathered at Foster gravesite, including Josiah Lilly and Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 410)
- Group gathered at the Foster gravesite for memorial services, including Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 411)
- Fletcher Hodges Jr. with Robert H. Caffee and an unidentified woman looking at the The Songs of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 412)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. and others observing a portrait of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 413)
- A group of men in cap and gown, including Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 414)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr., and others at a formal event (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 415)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr., and others seated outside (perhaps at the Jeanie Auditions?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 416)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr., presenting the winner of the Jeanie auditions with a package (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 417)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr., unveiling a small statue of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 418)
- Fletcher Hodges Jr. and others standing in front of a table (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 419)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr., at the Hall of Fame for Great Americans (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Folder 420)
  - Fletcher Hodges Jr. standing beside a bust at the Hall of Fame for Great Americans (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 420.01)
  - Fletcher Hodges and two unidentified men standing in front of a bust at the Hall of Fame for Great Americans (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 420.02)
  - Fletcher Hodges, Jr., and others laying a wreath at a bust at the Hall of Fame for Great Americans (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 420.03)
- Deane Root and Fletcher Hodges in the Foster museum, posed in front of the piano (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 421)
- Fletcher Hodges, Jr. with Japanese visitors (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 422)
  - Fletcher Hodges, Jr., on a bridge (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 422.01)
  - Profile of a young woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 422.02)
  - Fletcher Hodges, Jr., outside the Stephen Foster House (Greenfield Village?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 422.03)
  - Fletcher Hodges, Jr., with a Japanese visitor in the reading room (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 422.04)
- Deane Root and Fletcher Hodges, Jr. (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 423)
- Oval portrait of Hannah Harrison (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 424)
- James Snowden Hiekman, son of Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 425)
- Oval print of Jennie S. McKay (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 426)
- Betsey Snowden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 427)
- Blanche Snowden-Harrison (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 428)
- Blanche Snowden-Harrison (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 429)
- Blanche Snowden-Harrison (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 430)
- Blanche Snowden-Harrison (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 431)
- Blanche Snowden-Harrison (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 432)
- Caroline Allison Snowden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 433)
- Caroline Allison Snowden and Rebecca Snowden-Foster and others, Atlantic City, 1912 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 434)
- Edmund Snowden, brother of Francis Laird and Caroline Allison (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 435)
- Frank Laird Snowden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 436)
- James Olver's Snowden's residence built in 1895, Omaha, with Kirby Snowden and baby Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 437)
- Laddie Snowden, son of Francis Laird Snowden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 438)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg, oval framed print with locket of hair, daughter of James Olver Snowden (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 439)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 440)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 441)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg, age 5, 1896 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 442)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 443)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg and unidentified boy (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 444)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 445)
- Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 446)
- Mrs. Will (Marion) Stewart and baby Edith (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 447)
- Man with horse and buggy stopped on a dirt road (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 448)
- Engineering Department of the City of Omaha, September 6, 1890 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 449)
- Unidentified woman, possibly Marion Sage Snowden-Gagenburg, 1909 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 450)
- The F.F. Club: Reed Scull, Marshall Laid, George Ghyssels, Edith Ghyssels (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 451)
- "The Two Doggies," Pittsburgh, taken by Eliza O. Denniston, 1902 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 452)
- Mary Lightner Forsyth in a wood grain print mat (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 453)
- Memorial booklet for Madge Rowan Frost, 1925 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 1, Photos 454)